// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "x = '\\\\' print(len(x))",
    answer: "will print 2",
    options: [
      "will print 1",
      "will print 2",
      "will cause an error",
      "will print 3"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "hat output will appear after running the following snippet?",
    answer: "break the output line",
    options: [
      "The number of all the entities residing in the math module",
      "A string containing the fully qualified name of the module",
      "An error message",
      "A list of all the entities residing in the math module"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "The complied Python bytecode is stored in files which have their names ending with:",
    answer: "pyc",
    options: [
      "py",
      "p",
      "pc",
      "pyc"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which pip command would you use to uninstall a previously install package?",
    answer: "pip uninstall packagename",
    options: [
      "pip delete packagename",
      "pip –uninstall packagename",
      "pip –remove packagename",
      "pip uninstall packagename"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "If you want to fill a byte array with data read in from a stream, which method you can use?",
    answer: "The readinto() method",
    options: [
      "The read() method",
      "The readbytes() method",
      "The readfrom() method",
      "The readinto() method"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "A data structure described as LIFO is actually a:",
    answer: "stack",
    options: [
      "list",
      "stack",
      "heap",
      "tree"
    ]
  },
      {
    numb: 7,
    question: "A list of package’s dependencies can be obtained from pip using its command named:",
    answer: "the argument’s name specified along with is value",
    options: [
      "deps",
      "show",
      "dir",
      "list"
    ]
  },
   {
    numb: 8,
    question: "An operator able to check whether two values are equal is code as:",
    answer: "==",
    options: [
      "=",
    "!=",
      "==",
      "==="
    ]
  },
    {  
    numb: 9,
    question: "The pip list command presents a list of:",
    answer: "locally installed package",
    options: [
      "available pip commands",
      "outdated local package",
      "locally installed package",
      "all packages available at PyPI"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "A predefined Python variable that stores the current module name is called:",
    answer: "__name__",
    options: [
      "__name__",
      "__mod__",
      "__modname__",
      "__module__"
    ]
  },
];
